<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AnLinux</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="others">Others</string>
    <string name="features">Features</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="desktop_environment">Desktop Environment</string>
    <string name="uninstall">Uninstall</string>
    <string name="support">Support Devs</string>
    <string name="desktop_title">Setup Desktop</string>
    <string name="ssh_title">Setup SSH</string>
    <string name="watch_ads">Watch Ads</string>
    <string name="donation">Donation</string>
    <string name="_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="report">Report Error</string>
    <string name="ssh">SSH</string>
    <string name="patches">Patches</string>
    <string name="documentation">Documentation</string>
    <string name="step0">Please scroll down to see all steps if your device screen is small.</string>
    <string name="step1">Step 1 : Choose the distro you want to install, you can install multiple disto without conflict.</string>
    <string name="gui_step0">Please scroll down to see all steps if your device screen is small.\n\nRecommended having 2 GB spare before installing.\n\nWARNING: Only run this command inside the Linux System and not in Termux, otherwise it will not work!!!</string>
    <string name="gui_step1">Step 1 : Please choose a distro to setup the Desktop Environment</string>
    <string name="ssh_step0">Please scroll down to see all steps if your device screen is small.\n\nWARNING: This ssh server could not be connected from outside by other device unless you run the Linux distro with Run with Root Permission feature. Also please run this command inside the Linux System and not in Termux, otherwise it will not work!!!</string>
    <string name="ssh_step1">Step 1 : Please choose a distro to setup OpenSSH Server</string>
    <string name="patch_step0">Please scroll down to see all steps if your device screen is small.</string>
    <string name="patch_step1">Step 1 : Please choose a Patches</string>
    <string name="uninstall_step1">Step 1 : Choose the distro you want to UNINSTALL, the distro will be removed without a trace and could not be recovered.</string>
    <string name="press_again_to_exit">Please press again to exit application</string>
    <string name="about_content">AnLinux\nis a open source project intent to bring the access of Linux to Android platform.\n\nThe icon of this application is taken from https://www.iconfinder.com , which is created by user : "Alpár-Etele Méder", you can reach the icon author by clicking "ICON AUTHOR" button below.\n\nIf you are looking for the source code used in this app, click the SOURCE CODE button.\n\nIf you are looking for scripts and rootfs used in this app, please click the CONTENT SOURCE button, they are license under GPLv2.\n\nThanks for using this apps.\n\n\nRegards, EXA Lab</string>
    <string name="icon_author">Icon Author</string>
    <string name="source_code">Source Code</string>
    <string name="content_source_code">Content Source</string>
    <string name="choose">Choose</string>
    <string name="copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="Launch">Launch</string>
    <string name="ubuntu_beginner">Ubuntu (Recommended for Beginner)</string>
    <string name="xfce4_recommended">Xfce4 (Recommended)</string>
    <string name="first_warning_content">First of all, thanks for downloading AnLinux, below are some important parts, please read carefully.\n\n1. To keep the distro small and light weight for easy install, most distro except Arch Linux and Kali Nethunter are minimal rootfs, which means most package are not installed yet, you could install them according to your need, and stop asking if the distro is faked.\n\n2. All distro are installed in this directory: /data/data/com.termux/files/home , please make sure that you have enough space before installing package and don\'t blame the app for occupying your device space because you are the one controlling it.\n\n3. Some distro may not available due to your device architecture.\n\n4. Currently, all device except mips based will work, if you encountered any error such as Proot signal 6, or function not implemented, just go to the Patches feature in app and apply SECCOMP patch.\n\n5. NEVER install two Desktop Environment or Desktop Environment alongside Window Manager on a same distro, if you want to install another Desktop Environment or Window Manager, please reinstall the distro first. To do this, use "Uninstall" feature first, then reinstall it from Dashboard.\n\n\nThanks for reading, have a nice day :)</string>
    <string name="i_understand">I Understand</string>
    <string name="step2_cd">Step 2 : Please choose a distro first</string>
    <string name="step3_cd">Step 3 : Please choose a distro first</string>
    <string name="not_Supported">Not Supported</string>
    <string name="not_available">Not Available</string>
    <string name="same_arch_linux">Black Arch (Same as Arch Linux)</string>
    <string name="termux_not_Installed">Looks like Termux is not installed, but AnLinux only work with Termux v0.118.0.\n\nIMPORTANT: Please note that Termux in Google Play is deprecated and will not be updated in the future, Termux development team will now only update the package in F-droid, do you want to download it from F-droid now? (Scroll down and click Download APK to download Termux)</string>
    <string name="termux_not_fdroid">Looks like you are using the deprecated version of Termux, but AnLinux only work with Termux v0.118.0.\n\nIMPORTANT: Please note that Termux in Google Play is deprecated and will not be updated in the future, Termux development team will now only update the package in F-droid, do you want to download it from F-droid now? (Scroll down and click Download APK to download Termux)</string>
    <string name="uninstall_step2">Step 2 : Copy the command to clipboard : %1$s \n\n This should fully remove %2$s from Termux.</string>
    <string name="uninstall_step3">Step 3 : Start Termux, paste and enter the command to uninstall distro. Important: you will need to run this command inside Termux shell and NOT IN Linux Shell.</string>
    <string name="ashmem_step1">Please scroll down to see all steps if your device screen is small.\n\nWARNING: You should have wget installed on linux distro before proceeding, also remember only run this command inside the Linux System and not in Termux, otherwise it will not work!!!\n\nAbout Ashmem: System V shared memory emulation on Android, using ashmem. That includes shmget, shmat, shmdt and shmctl functions. It does not use Binder service, and does not link to Java libraries. It uses Linux sendmsg/recvmsg API instead to transfer file handlers.\n\nWhat it do: If you have error running some GUI programs, install this patch may solve the problem.\n\nHow to use: env LD_PRELOAD="/usr/local/lib/libandroid-shmem.so" linux_command"</string>
    <string name="ashmem_step2">Step 2 : Copy the command to clipboard : %1$s \n\nThis should install %2$s on your system.</string>
    <string name="ashmem_step3">Step 3 : Start Termux, paste and enter the command to install Patches. Remember: you will need to run ./start-*.sh to run the Linux System before using this command.</string>
    <string name="bug_encounter">If you encountered a bug, you can choose to open an issue on Github, or email us.</string>
    <string name="support_after_donation">Thanks for purchasing Donation Package, you can still watch video ads to support the developers, or continue to enjoy this app.</string>
    <string name="ask_for_donation">Thanks for using this app, do you want to support the developers?\n\nYou can choose to watch an ad video, which will remove advertisement for a day, or purchase a Donation Package on Play Store which remove the ads forever.</string>
    <string name="bug_report1">Bug Report</string>
    <string name="bug_report2">Please choose an app</string>
    <string name="no_video_ads">Currently no video ads available</string>
    <string name="ads_removed_temp">The ads are removed for today.</string>
    <string name="thanks_for_support">Thanks for your support!!!</string>
    <string name="documentation_prompt">Does not understand how it works?\n\nForgot how to start or exit distro, or forgot how to start the VNC Server(Desktop Enviroment)?\n\nThen this feature is for you, if you have these problem, or something you don\'t understand about this app, you could found some solution in the Github wiki pages.\n\nVisit now?</string>
    <string name="ssh_step2">Step 2 : Copy the command to clipboard : %1$s \n\n This should setup OpenSSH on the Linux System.</string>
    <string name="ssh_step3">Step 3 : Start Termux, paste and enter the command to setup SSH. Remember: you will need to run %1$s to run the Linux System before using this command.</string>
    <string name="de_step2_choose_first">Step 2: Please choose a Desktop Environment</string>
    <string name="de_step3_choose_first">Step 3: Please choose a Desktop Environment first</string>
    <string name="de_step4_choose_first">Step 4: Please choose a Desktop Environment first</string>
    <string name="gui_step2">Step 3 : Copy the command to clipboard : %1$s \n\nThis should setup %2$s and Tiger VNC on the Linux System.</string>
    <string name="gui_step3">Step 4 : Start Termux, paste and enter the command to install the desktop environment. Remember: you will need to run %1$s to run the Linux System before using this command.</string>
    <string name="dashboard_step2">Step 2 : Copy the command to clipboard : %1$s \n\nThis should install %2$s on your system, you can then run %3$s to run the command line.</string>
    <string name="dashboard_step3">Step 3 : Start Termux, paste and enter the command to install distro. Remember: you will need to run %1$s to run the command line.</string>
    <string name="dashboard_step2_arch">Step 2 : Copy the command to clipboard : %1$s \n\nThis should install %2$s on your system, you can then run %3$s to run the command line.\n\nAfter that, you will need to run: chmod 755 additional.sh &amp;&amp; ./additional.sh to setup resolv.conf and pacman-key, otherwise network connection and pacman wont work!!! (First time only)</string>
    <string name="dashboard_step3_arch">Step 3 : Start Termux, paste and enter the command to install distro. Remember: you will need to run ./start-arch.sh to run the command line, after that, you will also need to run ./additional.sh to setup resolv.conf and pacman-key, otherwise network connection and pacman wont work!!! (First time only)</string>
    <string name="dashboard_step2_blackarch">Note: Please run this command inside Arch Linux shell to enable BlackArch Repository (Arch Linux need to be installed first).\n\nStep 2 : Copy the command to clipboard : %1$s</string>
    <string name="dashboard_step3_blackarch">Step 3 : Start Termux, enter Arch Linux shell by running ./start-arch.sh, then paste and enter the command to install BlackArch Repo. Remember: you will need to run ./start-arch.sh to enter Arch Linux shell first before using the command above.</string>
    <string name="arch_linux_warning_content">Arch Linux image is bigger than other distro (Around 400 MB), and may cost a lot of device space after decompressing. Having spare space over 1.5GB is highly recommended before installing.\n\n\nNote:\n\n1. Tar may produce an error while extracting the image such as: tar: Ignoring unknown extended header keyword \'SCHILY.fflags\', it is not harmful, simply ignore it.\n\n2. Arch Linux image is hosted on an external server, the link may broken in some special case, Please email the developers at exalabdevelopers@gmail.com if encountered this issue.</string>
    <string name="nethunter_warning_content">Woah, wait wait wait.\n\nSorry for the interrupt, here are some warning:\n\n1. Kali Nethunter image itself is around 1GB, after decompressing, it will cost more space, it is advice to have 5GB free space before installing.\n\n2. Decompressing the image require some time (Around 10 minutes.)\n\n3. Desktop environment won\'t work, DO NOT use command for Kali in Nethunter.\n\n4. Nethunter image has not been updated more than a year, some component is broken, if you want an up-to-date, personalized experience, choose normal Kali distro instead.</string>
    <string name="run_with_root">Run with Root Permission</string>
    <string name="root_content0">Please scroll down to see all steps if your device screen is small.\n\nPlease note that running wrong command in Root mode could damage the whole Android OS!\n\nFirst, this feature is for Root Users only, if you never heard of Root, Superuser, SU, SuperSU, Magisk, then you should not use this feature.\n\nI understand that the purpose of most user use this app is to INSTALL LINUX DISTRO WITHOUT ROOT ACCESS.\n\nBut, If your device have root access, you still want to run it without root? To be clear, having root access could have lots of benefit, especially when running high permission software such as penetration testing tools.\n\nFor those don\'t know how to do it, Termux could run it root mode, simply start Termux, and type su command, but that won\'t work as running ./start-*.sh command after the su call will result in PRoot not found error.\n\nBut this word are not exist to tell you that, of course, we have a solution to RUN LINUX DISTRO WITH ROOT ACCESS, just follow the instruction below:</string>
    <string name="root_content1">1. Press the button to copy the command: pkg install tsu -y &amp;&amp; hash -r</string>
    <string name="root_content2">Start Termux, paste and enter the command above, after that, you could simply run the tsu command, then run ./start-*.sh like usual.</string>
    <string name="su_warning_content">Sorry for the bothering, but this is important, so please take a look as we show this one time only.\n\nRunning Linux as Root has lots of benefit, but also contain dangerous that could wipe out whole Android OS if you don\'t know how to use it.\n\nPlease beware of what you are doing, author are not responsible if you run some harmful command and bricked your device, also please make sure you should NEVER fire up the Root terminal and run some command like rm -rf /* for experimental purpose.\n\nBy proceeding, you agree to those terms.</string>
    <string name="i_agree">I Agree</string>
    <string name="command_copied">Command copied</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="seccomp_step1">Please scroll down to see all steps if your device screen is small.\n\nWARNING: Only run this if you encountered error such as Proot signal 6, or function not implemented.</string>
    <string name="seccomp_step2">Step 2 : Copy the command to clipboard : echo "export PROOT_NO_SECCOMP=1" >> .bashrc &amp;&amp; hash -r</string>
    <string name="seccomp_step3">Step 3 : Start Termux, paste and enter the command to install Patches. Remember: you will need this command directly inside Termux and not in the Linux distro, otherwise it will not work.</string>
    <string name="rootfs_download">Download Rootfs (Offline use)</string>
    <string name="rootfs_download_content">This feature is to download the rootfs(Or simply know as distro) for offline use only, if you want to install distro normally you should install it from "Dashboard", not here.\n\nSome users would want to download rootfs for investigation or learning purpose, we created this feature so users could easily find the location to download.\n\nClicking the Button below would open a webpage on Github where rootfs are stored:\nhttps://github.com/EXALAB/AnLinux-Resources/tree/master/Rootfs\nwithout further notification.</string>
    <string name="view">View</string>
    <string name="window_manager">Window Manager</string>
    <string name="wm_step0">Please scroll down to see all steps if your device screen is small.\n\nWindows Manager is a GUI similar as Desktop Environment, but it is much smaller and lighter, if you prefer something more light weight and legacy feel, Window Manager is for your, otherwise use Desktop Environment instead.\n\nRecommended having 1.5 GB spare before installing.\n\nWARNING: Only run this command inside the Linux System and not in Termux, otherwise it will not work!!!</string>
    <string name="wm_step1">Step 1 : Please choose a distro to setup the Window Manager</string>
    <string name="wm_step2_choose_first">Step 2: Please choose a Window Manager</string>
    <string name="wm_step3_choose_first">Step 3: Please choose a Window Manager first</string>
    <string name="wm_step4_choose_first">Step 4: Please choose a Window Manager first</string>
    <string name="wm_title">Setup Window Manager</string>
    <string name="patches_step2_choose_first">Step 2: Please choose a Patches first</string>
    <string name="patches_step3_choose_first">Step 3: Please choose a Patches first</string>
    <string name="heavy_de">Heavy DE</string>
    <string name="heavy_de_note">Heavy Desktop Environment was a feature that let you install Desktop Environment that are very beautiful and popular among desktop Linux users. But they require lots of space, resource and ram to work.\n\nSo before installing, please make sure you have at lease:\n\n5GB of space\n4GB ram</string>
    <string name="heavy_de_step1">Step 1 : Please choose a Desktop Environment</string>
    <string name="heavy_de_step2_choose_first">Step 2: Please choose a Distro</string>
    <string name="heavy_de_step3_choose_first">Step 3: Please choose a Distro first</string>
    <string name="heavy_de_step4_choose_first">Step 4: Please choose a Distro first</string>
    <string name="heavy_de_step0">Please scroll down to see all steps if your device screen is small.\n\nWARNING: Only run this command inside the Linux System and not in Termux, otherwise it will not work!!!</string>
</resources>
